Adam Pham



Full-Stack Developer

Download PDF Version Here!

◆ Marangaroo, PerthWestern Australia, 6064

lee

thaihoangpham2008@gmail.com

- **1** 0447 308 708
- ☐ ThiHoangPham
- adam_thai_hoang90

Skills

- **፱** HTML5
- **∃** CSS3
- Js JavaScript
- nede Node.js
- MySQL

Summary

Spent almost 6 year working in Supermarkets Industry, I am taking the opportunity to start learning the IT skills again, it gonna be a brand new page of my life where is in the world of web development. Challenge, Difficult, but will be Successful.

Experience

Woolworths Supermarkets Cottesloe. Cottesloe, Western

Australia

Assistant Produce Manager - August, 2021 - PRESENT

• Great Teamwork in Woolies Fresh Produce to bring out the best quality fruits and vegs go with best services.

IGA Supermarkets Kingsley. Kingsley, Western Australia

Assistant Produce - November, 2019 - July, 2021

 Worked as team leader, bring out a great value fresh produce and great customer service.

IGA Supermarkets Riverton. Willetton, Western Australia

Assistant Produce Manager - November, 2019 - July, 2021

• Started working in Produce in IGA. Gained almost 4 years experience in Supermarket customers services, working in team.

Nam Truong Hoang Co., Ltd. Dong Da, Hanoi, Vietnam

Sales Marketing Executive - April, 2014 - Septemper, 2015

• Managed Marketing Online Campaign: Facebook Ads, Google Adwords, SEO.

Viettel Telecom. Long Bien District, Hanoi, Vietnam

Technical Salesman - September, 2013 - March, 2014

• Set and run marketing online plan: Google Adwords, Facebook Ads Campaign, Advised customers about Viettel telecommunications service.

KTM Duong Men Co., Ltd. Thanh Xuan District, Hanoi, Vietnam

Information Technology Assistant - September, 2013 - March, 2014

Maintained computer networks and communication systems, installed office software

Education

The University of Western Australia. Perth, Australia

Coding Bootcamp - Full Stack Developer - August, 2021 - PRESENT

 Have learnt and mastered variables of computer programming languages such as HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Java, jQuery, Node.js, Responsive Design, Heroku, Git, MySQL, and more...

Hanoi University of Science and Technology. Hai Ba Trung

Hanoi, Vietnam

Network and System Administration - 2008 - 2009